brinkzone.com 2019-12-21

# Privacy Policy | BrinkZone.com

## _Who we are_

 _Our website address is: http://brinkzone.com._

##  _What personal data we collect and why we collect it_

###  _Comments_

 _When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection._

 _An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment._

###  _Media_

 _If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website._

###  _Contact forms_

 _Contact forms are used to collect email information. We may also collect data provided such as your phone number, date of birth, full name and address and email address if asked for._

###  _Cookies_

 _If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year._

 _If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser._

 _When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed._

 _If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day._

 _Other cookies that may be set are functional cookies from YouTube, Google Analytics, etc. These cookies have predetermined amount of time, most cookies on this site are 365 day cookies, though some are less._

###  _Embedded content from other websites_

 _Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website._

 _These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website._

###  _Analytics_

 _We use analytics to judge the traffic or our site and where it comes from and use it to serve the best content based on this traffic. These analytics will include IP addresses and Geolocation of those addresses.  
_

##  _Who we share your data with_

 _We share data with Google, Aweber, Inc, and other third parties that we use purchase software through. We do not SELL your information.  
_

##  _How long we retain your data_

 _If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue._

 _For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal identifying information (PII) they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators and editors can also see and edit that information._

##  _What rights you have over your data_

 _If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes._

##  _Where we send your data_

 _Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service, and with automated firewall services, Geolocation and Google Analytics._

##  _Contact information_

 _For information or questions about Brinkzone Privacy policy_

 _Will Brink – Contact@brinkzone.com  
_
